Privacy Policy for Block This! - FREE (Android app)
===================================================

(Last updated on September 19, 2015 and effective as of this date)

This privacy statement ("Privacy Policy") governs your use of online services and/or websites and software applications for mobile devices (together "Services") that are created and/or provided by Block This Sava Georgiev ("Us" or "We"). The Privacy Policy only governs information that has been provided to Us and/or automatically collected by the Services either directly or through embedded technologies within the Services, not information that you provide to third parties or such information that is made publicly available.

We take privacy seriously here at Block This. And we know that you don't want to wade through a bunch of legalese, so here is our privacy policy in plain English.

BASICS
------

We are not spammers and we will never sell your information to any third party ever. All information that we obtain from you through the use of our service is used in order to provide basic functionality or enhance your experience of this product. Our DNS servers keep no server logs or any other means to identify, recognize or monitor user traffic, except for an aggregated report of amount of blocked and successful requests, average response times and other similar statistics which help in keeping the service stable and running.

DATA WE COLLECT
---------------

**User Provided Information**

We may collect certain personal information that you choose to provide to Us either by using the Services, in the process of communication with Us, when you contact Us for help or when you provide Us with feedback, or in any other way, such as by e-mail or telephone. Such information may include your name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number, year of birth, gender. We may use the personal information that you choose to provide to Us to respond to your questions and/or feedback or to contact you from time to time to provide you with important information or with required notices.

**Automatically Collected Information**

The Services may collect, either directly or through embedded technologies, certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of device you use, your unique device ID, your carrier user ID, operating system, your preferences and/or settings, and information about the way you use the Services.

DO THIRD PARTIES SEE AND/OR HAVE ACCESS TO THE COLLECTED INFORMATION?
---------------------------------------------------------------------

We will not share your information with third parties except as described in this privacy statement. We may disclose User Provided Information and Automatically Collected Information:

\- as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process;

\- when We believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;

\- with our trusted services providers who work on our behalf and do not have any right to use personal information or other information We share with them beyond what is necessary to assist Us. You hereby consent to our sharing of User Provided Information and Automatically Collected Information with our service providers.

THIRD PARTIES WITH WHOM WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION
-------------------------------------------------

**Crashlytics**

We use Crashlytics to report to us when the app crashes so that we can fix these crashes as soon as possible. We don't send any information to Crashlytics, but they may collect information via their SDK.

You can view Crashlytics' privacy policy here: [http://try.crashlytics.com/terms/](http://try.crashlytics.com/terms/)

INFORMATION PROTECTION
----------------------

We use reasonable efforts to help protect your personal information against unauthorized access and unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction. However, we cannot guarantee that your personal information will be absolutely protected. For example, your personal information may be affected by actions outside of our control, such as computer "hacking" and physical theft. You acknowledge that you provide your personal information at your own risk.

CHILDREN
--------

We do not use the Services to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided Us with information without their consent, he or she should contact Us at info@block-this.com. We will then delete such information from our files within a reasonable time.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
------------------------------

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time. We will post all changes to this Privacy Policy on this page and will indicate at the top of the page the modified policy's effective date.

YOUR CONCENT
------------

By using the Services, you hereby consent to this Privacy Policy and agree to its terms and to the described practices.

CONTACT US
----------

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@block-this.com.

© Block This 2015
